University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2018; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.; 505 Digital Files
  - 2001-2002 Academic Year Legislation, 2001 July-2002 June
    - 0102-13 Graduate Academic Council Joint Master of Arts in History (MA) and Master of Arts In Public Policy (MPP) Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 0102-14 Conversion of Dual Degree Programs: BA or BS/MLS to BA or BS/MSLS, MA/MLS to MA/MSIS Historyor English Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 0102-15 Combined BA/MA in Women's Studies Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 0102-16 [record missing], 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 0102-17 Proposed Amendment A (LISC) Approved 9-4-02, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 2000-2001 Academic Year Legislation, 2000 July-2001 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 0001-01 Partnership Agreement for the Establishment of Army Reserve Officer's Training (ROTC) Instruction at the Unlversity at Aibany EPC Approved 02-27-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-02 University at Albany Policy for the Responsible Use of Information Technology -- LISC Approved 02-27-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-01R Resolution for Conslderation by the University Senate, Unieersity at Albany, On the Implementatlon of General Education Programs University Senate Executive Committee Approved 02-12-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Proposal to Establish an Interdisciplinary Undergraduate Major in International Studies Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-04 Undergraduate Academic Council The New General Education Program Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-05 Proposal to Change Graduate Academic Policies Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-06 Graduate Academic Council Proposal to Establish an Interdisciplinary Graduate Certificate in Nonprofit Management and Leadership Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-07 Undergraduate Academic Council and Graduate Academic Council Joint Bachelors/Masters Programs Linking the M.S. in Health Policy and Management with Undergraduate Programs in Psychology (B.A.), Sociology (S.A.), and Economics (B.A. and B.S.) Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-08 Undergraduate Academic Council Curricular Revision from the School of Education Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-09 Undergraduate Academic Council Proposed Faculty-Initiated lnterdisciplinary Minor in Bioethics Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 0001-10 ULC Principles for a Just Community Changes Approved 06-08-01, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1999-2000 Academic Year Legislation, 1999 July-2000 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 9900-01 Undergraduate Academic Council Admission Requirement for Sociology Majors Approved 12-20-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-02 Undergraduate Academic Council Deregistration of Undergraduate Students Lacking Course Prequisites 12-02-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of the General Education Requirements Approved 12-06-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-01R Undergraduate Academic Council Resolution Concerning Freshman Writing Approved 12-16-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-02R Undergraduate Academic Council Resolution Concerning the Quality of General Education Approved 12-16-99, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-04 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision of Procedures for Undergraduate Withdrawals from the University Approved 03-03-00, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 9900-05 Postmatriculation Transfer Credit with Grade of 0 Approved 03-03-00, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1998-1999 Academic Year Legislation, 1998 July-1999 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 9899-01 Undergraduate Academic Coucil Revision of College-Level Examination Program Approved 01-14-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-02 Graduate Academic Council Changes in Graduate Policies Pertaining to Residence Study, Statute of Limitations and Transfer Credit Regulation Applicable to Master's Degree Study Approved 01-14-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-01R General Education, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-03 Proposed Composition of the Council on Libraries, Information Systems and Computing Approved 02-22-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-04 Proposed Composition of the Council on Academic Freedom and Ethics Approved 02-22-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-05 Faculty-Initiated Proposal for a Bachelor of Arts Degree in Earth and Atmospheric Sciences Approved 03-29-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-06 Graduate Academic Council Reccomendation for Change in Master Degrees in Information Sciences Approved 03-29-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-07 Educational Policy Council Assessment of University Educational Enhancement Programs Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-08 Educational Policy Council Transfer of Faculty Across Academic Units Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-09 Graduate Academic Council Revised Policy on Doctoral "Full-Time Study in Residence" Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-10 Graduate Academic Council Recommendation for Proposed Dual Jointly Registered Degree Program in Social Work and Law Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-11 Undergraduate Academic Council Changes in Undergraduate Withdrawl and Reentry Policies Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-12 Undergraduate Academic Council Changes in Undergraduate Deregistration Policy Approved 05-03-99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 9899-13 Undergraduate Academic Council Revisions to "D" Balancing Policy for Transfer Students, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1997-1998 Academic Year Legislation, 1997 July-1998 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 9798-01R Approved 10-20-97 [record missing], 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-02R Approved 12-8-97 [record missing], 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-03R Reaffirm the University's Principle's of a Just Community Approved 12-08-97, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-04R Council on Libraries Upgrading the Computer User Rooms Approved 03-30-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-05R University Community Council Physical Education Building and Recreation and Convocation Center Hours Approved 07-30-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-01 University Community Council Use of Non-Powered Wheeled Vehicles, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-02 Undergraduate Academic Council Senior Resident Requirements Approved 07-30-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-03 Undergradute Academic Council Regulations and Requirements for Students Admitted to the University at Albany for a second Baccalaureate Degree Approved 07-30-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 9798-04 Graduate Academic Council MA in Women's Studies Approved 07-30-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1996-1997 Academic Year Legislation, 1996 July-1997 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 9697-01 Undergraduate Academic Council Ammendment to the Criteria fir Grade Point Average Required Approved 01-14-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-02A Undergradute Academic Council Ammendment to S Grade Implementation Approved 05-05-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-03 Undergraduate Academic Council Establishment of a New Degree Program Bachelor of Arts in Chemistry Approved 01-14-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-04 Undergraduate Academic Council Amendment in the Criteria for Dean's List and Dean's Commendation for Part-time Students Approved 03-18-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-05 Dual Jointly Registered Master's Degree in Social Work (M.S.W) and Master of Arts in Social Science (M.A.S.S) With Binghamton University (S.U.N.Y) Approved 03-18-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-02 Amendment to the Grading Criteria At the Undergraduate Level Approval 01-14-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-06 Proposal to the Reclassify Current NCAA Divisions II Membership to Division IA (Footbal, Division IAA) Approved 05-05-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-07 Honors Program in Linguistics Approved 06-19-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 9697-08 Honors Program in Computer Science Approved 6-19-97, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1995-1996 Academic Year Legislation, 1995 July-1996 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 9596-01R Project Renaissance Passe, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-01 Undergraduate Academic Council - Pre-Regisration of the Major in Greek Approved 10-05-95, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-02 Graduate Academic Council - MS in Biodiversity Conversation and Polciy Approved 11-07-95, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-03 Graduate Academic Council - Optional Advisement for Nondegree Graduate Students Approved 12-22-95, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-04 Undergraduate Academic Council - Establishment of a Faculty-Initiated Interdisciplinary Major with Concentration in urban Studies and Planning Approved 03-19-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-01R EC Project Renaissance Approved 02-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-05 UCC Smoking Policy Approved 08-06-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-02R CPCA Council and Promotion Continuing Appointments Approved 05-05-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-06 SAC/UCC Council Merge Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-07 Undergraduate Academic Council Policy Revisions for UGR Degree Requirements Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-08 Undergraduate Academic Council Revision in the UGR Program Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-09 Undergraduate Academic Council Minor in Urban Education Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-10 Graduate Academic Council Graduate Certificate in Urban Education Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 9596-11 Graduate Academic Council De-registration of Master's Program Approved 06-12-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1994-1995 Academic Year Legislation, 1994 July-1995 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 9495-01R Commencement Separate Undergraduate and Graduate Ceremonies Approved 12-12-96, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-02R Personal and collective security and Campus Together Day, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-03R **Resolution on On-Une Accessibility Approved 5-8-95, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-04R ** Executive Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-05R University Smoking Policy Approved 5-8-95, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-06R Computer hook-Ups, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-01 Joint Seven year Program in Biology/Optometry with SUNY Optometry Approved 12-20-94, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 9495-02 Establishment of a New Degree Program: Bachelor of Science in Actuarial and Mathematical Sciences Approved 12-20-94, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1993-1994 Academic Year Legislation, 1993 July-1994 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 9394-01 Undergraduate Leave for Approved Study Policy Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic CounciI Approved 11-19-93, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 9394-02 Principles of Teaching Responsibility Introduced by: EducationaI Policy Council Approved 4-7-94, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 9394-03 Reclassify Current NCAA Division III Membership to Division III Introduced by: Educational Policy Council Approved 4-25-94, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 9394-04 Ph.D. in Biometry and Statistics Introduced by: Graduate Academic PoIicy Approved 5-3-94, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 9394-05 Proposal to Eliminate Student Opted S/U Grading Approved 5-3-94, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1992-1993 Academic Year Legislation, 1992 July-1993 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 9293-01 Commencement Introduced by: Senate Executive Committee Approved 11-16-92, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-01R Voluntary Teaching Oay (Resolution) Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic CounciI, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-02 Revision of Requirements for Completion of the General Education Honors Program Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic CounciI Approved 1-5-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-03 Revision of Requirements for Completion of the General Education Honors Program (for students who matriculate in FaII 1933 and thereafter) Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 1-5-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-04 Policy to Deregister Students Who Do Not Attend Class Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 1-5-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-05 Revision of Student Senator Elections Introduced by: Senate Executive Committee Approved 3-9-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-06 Undergraduate Leave of Absence Policy Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 7-1-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-07 Ph.D. in Epidemiology Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 6-7-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-08 Criteria for Capping or Restricting a Major Introduced by: CounciI on Educational Policy Approved 5-25-93, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 9293-09 Doctor of Public Healtth (Dr.P.H.) Introduced by: Graduate Academic CounciI, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1991-1992 Academic Year Legislation, 1991 July-1992 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 9192-01 General Education Program Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-02 Faculty-Initiated Major in Art History Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 02-12-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-03 Ph. D. Program in Philosophy Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 02-12-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-04 Faculty-initiated Major in East Asian Studies Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-01-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-05 Revision to Policy on Advising of Graduate Students Introduced by: Graduate Academic CounciI Approved 05-18-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-06 Revision to Policy on English Language Proficiency of International Graduate Students Introduced by Graduate Academic Council Approved 05-18-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-07 PoIicy on Existing "I" Grades in Graduate Courses, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-08 Revision to Policy on Admission to Doctoral Candidacy, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-09 Faculty-initiated Major in Human Biology Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-18-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-10 Revision to Policy on Credit Limit Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-18-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 9192-11 PoIicy to Deregister Students who FaiI to Attend Classes Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-18-92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1990-1991 Academic Year Legislation, 1990 July-1991 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 9091-01R Senate Still Strongly Supports Making the Senate Rep. to Council's Voting, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-01 Commencement Introduced by: Council on Educational Policy Approved 12-05-90, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-02 Proposal to Change the Degree Designation for the Doctoral Program in Curriculum and Instruction from the Ed.D. to the Ph.D. Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 04-04-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-03 Proposal to Change the Degree Designation for the Doctoral Program in Reading from the Ed.D. to the Ph.D. Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 04-04-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-04 Proposed Ph.D. Program in History Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 04-04-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-05 Amendment to 3081-01: Guidelines for Academic Calendars Introduced by: Council on Educational Policy Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-06 Readmission Procedures for Undergraduates Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-07 Qualitative Academic Retention Standards for Undergraduates Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-08 General Education Exemptions and Waivers for Transfer Students Introduced by Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-09 Human Diversity Amendment Introduced by: Undergraduate Aeademic Council Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-10 ROTC Credit for Undergraduates Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 04-15-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-11 Special Talent Admissions Program Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-21-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-12 Interdisciplinary Undergraduate Major in Biochemistry and Molecular Biology Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-21-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-13 Interdisciplinary Undergraduate Major in Japanese Studies Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 05-21-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 9091-14 Policy on Allocation of University-Wide Authoring Stations Introduced by: Council on Libraries, Information Systems and Computing Approved 05-21-91, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1989-1990 Academic Year Legislation, 1989 July-1990 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 8990-01 College-based Commencement Exercises for Undergraduate Introduced by: Educational Policy Council - Approved 10-05-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-02 MS Program in Information Science Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council - Approved 10-20-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-03 University Policy on Misconduct in Research Introduced by: Council on Research - Approved 11-14-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-04 MS in Health Policy and Management Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council - Approved 12-18-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-05 Master of Public Health (M.P.H.) Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council - Approved 12-18-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-06 Termination of University Community Council Introduced by: Executive Committee - Approved 11-20-89, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-07 Reorganization of Senate Councils Introduced by: Executive Committee - Approved 03-01-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-08 Registration Policy Affecting Seniors Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 01-23-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-09 Revision of the General Education Honors Program Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 01-23-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-10 BA in Religious Studies Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 01-23-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-11 Summer Session Withdrawals Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 03-14-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-12 Adding A Course Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 03-21-90 as amended, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-13 Policies on Graduation Credits Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 03-14-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-14 Cross-Listing of Courses Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 03-14-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-15 Ph.D. Program in English Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council - Approved 03-05-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-16 Change in Council Name Introduced by: Executive Committee - Approved 03-01-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-17 Transfer of "D" Grades Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-18 "S"Grade Limitations Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council - Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-19 Amendment to the Residence Requirement Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-20 UNI 180 - Undergraduate Supervised Research Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-21 Admission Requirements for Undergraduate Major in Psychology Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-22 BA/BS-MBA Five Year Prograrn in Business Administration Introduced by: Undergraduate Acadmic Council Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-23 Academic Integrity Introduced by: Executive Committee Approved 05-08-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-24 Resolution on Division I Athletics Introduced by: Executive Committee Approved 05-03-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-25 Policy on Allocation of Main-Frame Computing Resources Introduced by: Council on Libraries, Information, Systems and Computers Approved 06-22-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-26 Inter-Disciplinary Undergraduate Major in Information Science Introduced by: Undergraduate Academic Council Approved 06-22-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-27 Ph.D. Pro gram in French Studies Introduced by: Graduate Academic Council Approved 06-22-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-28 Criteria for Promotion and Continuing Appointment Introduced by: Council on Promotion and Continuing Appointment Approved 06-22-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-29 Assessment Report - University at Albany Introduced by: Council on Educational Policy Approved 06-22-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 8990-30 Principles of a Just Community Introduced by: University Senate Approved 05-21-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1988-1989 Academic Year Legislation, 1988 July-1989 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 8889-01 Period of Service for Members of the Promotions Council Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments Executive Committee - Approved 10-21-88, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-02 Position of Chair of the Program Review Committee Executive Committee - Approved 10-03-88, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-03 Resolution on Freedom of Research Activity Research Council - Approved 5-16-89, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-04 Amendment to University Policy on Freedom of Expression Council on Academic Freedom - Approved 7-31-1989, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-05 Resolution University Community Council on Spirit and Loyalty Toward the University, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-06 Interdisciplinary BA Major in Human Biology Undergraduate Academic Council - Approved 7-20-89, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 8889-07 Human Diversity Requirement Senators Edwin Reilly and Carson Carr - Approved 08-02-89, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1987-1988 Academic Year Legislation, 1987 July-1988 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 8788-01 Department of Latin American and Caribbean Sts Proposed MA. Program in Latin American and Caribbean Studies Program Abstract Graduate Academic Council - Approved 10-9-87, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)